this is sankara she likes to be picked up you know who else was supposed to be on a book tour
right now yeah i was supposed to be on a book tour i was about to be going on a book tour
i was about to be going on a book tour and then i was like no i don't do y'all understand how
absolutely insane it is to be dropping a book right now about your failed campaign where you
blame everybody in the book but you like that's the part that i'm trying to understand how none of
y'all like okay not none of y'all but a lot of folks they just don't that is like that's not
come on y'all you dropped a book that blames everybody for you not winning except for you
and at no point talks about what you would have done like it's one thing to be like they didn't
want me to talk about palestine but now fuck them free palestine like that would make sense
i'm not gonna evict i'm not gonna call her a victim i don't like that term i don't like when people
call somebody saying shit a victim but ultimately even if everybody was on some bullshit i'm like
how how are you not on some bullshit i like how people come in here and say things like
why are you smearing her smearing somebody is when you are lying about them smearing somebody is when
you are making a choice to defame somebody without good reason i have a good reason as a citizen of this
nation for feeling some type of way that the former vice president who uses black identity politics
in everything she does is parading around the united states in the middle of a time of turmoil
selling a book yes i have an issue with that i have an issue with the former vice president of the united
united states a black woman the first black woman to do so raising one billion dollars in campaign funds
and then going on a book tour less than a year later while the nation is suffering from inflation
over 300 000 black women are said to have lost their jobs since trump came into power immigrants are
losing their families and their lives and their livelihoods and you're on a book tour
you're on a book tour you're you just signed to a talent agency and you've said nothing
and done nothing with your massive following and platform to mobilize people
in how to stand up for the what's going on and people keep saying what do you expect her to do
and i i want to understand why you don't expect anything from her i want to understand why you were
about to put somebody in power that you don't expect anything from i'll never understand this i'll just
never understand that you could be on your platform you could be saying listen um we need to be raising
our voices for the global summit matilla except did someone just ask if the american population is 300 000
people did you just ask that you didn't ask that i'm gonna i'm just gonna pretend you didn't ask that
because that's a wildly idiotic question um so i just you know i'm i'm not really
grasping why and this and i keep harping on it because if we're not making demands of people when
they're getting into office and we're not making demands of people when they're in office and we're
not making demands of people when they're out of office what is the point i'm trying to understand
the point because i don't know what y'all i i don't know what the goal is because i see it all the time
i see it every time oh don't don't question them until they get in all right now they're in don't
questioning while they're in you know they they trying to do what they can do they can only do so
much and then when they get out they you say well you know they're a private citizen now someone just
says she wanted to tell her story because trump is actively erasing our history what are you fucking
talking about bro kamala harris's story of losing the election is not our story oh my god
then i just saw someone in here say that's why i'm a liberal because the dnc y'all gotta learn what
these words mean because you have to be able to properly identify yourself y'all gotta be able to
properly understand your political stance and that it is not associated with uh it really shouldn't be
associated with a party no kamala harris's story is not our story kamala harris
is the was the vice president of the united states y'all want to make things just about race
class is massive and there's nothing about kamala harris's story of losing the election
that i see myself in that's not that's not i'm not that's not our story i don't so i'm not she said
i want to tell my story before anyone else can that's important to history is it i'm gonna just give you
some insight into what she could be doing with this tour okay if she was really trying to not
just get money from y'all she wouldn't even be charging for people to attend her book events
she would charge for the books but she would not charge for people to attend the book events
if she was really about the people and not about making money off these books
she would be going to black bookstores because that's her audience all these black women professionals
who were like i'm getting on this call because black women power shannon said i feel like maybe you
knew you two need to have a one-on-one talk i've had a one-on-one talk with kamala harris and i told her
exactly what she was doing wrong and then she proceeded to do it further and also the dnc little
uh matt the d the dnc little minions went around smearing my voice and attempting to discredit me
please y'all think i'm talking about somebody i ain't never met before so again if this was really
about i had to get this story out before anybody else did then that's what it would be about it
wouldn't be about sitting down with a zionist like aaron parnas it wouldn't be about telling
pro-palestinian supporters to be quiet to be quiet be quiet to then stand up and say what's happening
to palestinians is outrageous and that's it that's it and the fact that y'all don't see this is
telling that we are so deeply embedded in narcissism that we can't recognize it we can't
i can tell you i could not see myself dropping my book where i'm looking up into the sky
thanking god for for making it through my own journey while all of us are here
in the quicksand now how that work why do i need to talk about arena reserved skyya what is there to say
she met an unfortunate end the end she met an unfortunate end and perhaps if there were actual
access to free health care she wouldn't have met an unfortunate end because the individual who took
her life would have had access to getting mental health support yes your pre-order was canceled i just
sat here and said i chose not to put my book out all right i'm about to take a class
um because i'm expanding my knowledge so you all have a great evening and remember it's free
palestine till is backwards remember that politicians are supposed to be activists black politicians are
supposed to be activists and remember that when you act as if political activism is an oxymoron
well you have been indoctrinated figure that out
will be no cultural on you zap other people can use the other people like that i don't have to
need that because iblowing it i хотしく keep faithfully and you have to strolling it off this
one day so i haven't seen him Cave in the 2 or time and i don't have time for it to survive